Lootera Kabaddi can be done
tonight Nishan Sir, health insurance is
very important in today's time, otherwise what happened,
you saved money, I know it hurt a lot, I
worked very hard, I don't know what all
and saved a lot of money, by working for 10 years, you
saved 10-20 lakh rupees,
somehow saved it and if
someone gets sick, then this experiment is
over, you were in 10 days, 15 days, how many people are
practically able to relate to this,
everyone is able to do it and that you have
Sanjay Mishra, you are able to
relax, but there are
people who have taken 100 health
insurance, oh I think you might have taken it in
your name,
how much is known,
because if you take more cover then
you do not have to pay much premium, the
margin is extra, it covers the
entire family, half of it goes to
all your children, this is called
health insurance, medical insurance,
it should be there in the way,
what happens, those who have not got this section cleaned,
you leave it  We can take
that person who is with me,
if something happens to us then we cannot say
that we are dead, so what happens in such a situation, a lot of money gets
lost very quickly, what else gets
lost, and what happens is
taking a loan, you will have to take it very generously,
what does it mean to repay the loan, that
you can never become a farmer again in your life, do you
even understand how big the problem is
and how complicated it is that you will never be able to save
money in your life, whatever you
earn, all that you earn is spent
in repaying the loan, now you will take it from the bank
balance or from any friends from here, from here, from as many
people as you can, if not then you will
spoil this friendship,
and one more thing which has come till here, one more
thing, one more mistake we make, we want to
make money, always keep doing that, wherever there is
talk of quick money, invest so much money, you will get so much
money in so much time, this will go, run away from
there, you are on the contrary and do
not stop brothers, you gave it by mistake, many such
schemes are going on in the market
and unlimited and crores of people have
earned money from these  We are in a dilemma,
now let's come to another point that
when did we add money smartly, when did
we not block the money at unnecessary places, so
if you take any endowment
insurance plan where your annual sum is
going to 50,000, then ₹50 is for the next 20 years, you
understand, so we played smartly here, got
term insurance,
saved money from there, so now the money that is saved is in this
computer.